expanding is the task of taking a shorter piece of text
展开的任务是选取较短的文本
such as a set of instructions or a list of topics
例如一组指令或一个主题列表
and having the larger language model
拥有更大的语言模型
generate a longer piece of text such as
生成较长的文本，例如
an email or an essay about some topic
一封电子邮件或一篇关于某个主题的文章
there are some great uses of this
这有一些很好的用途
such as if you use a large language model
例如，如果您使用大型语言模型
as a brainstorming partner
作为一个头脑风暴的伙伴
but
但
I just also want to acknowledge that there are some
我也想承认有一些
problematic use cases of this
有问题的用例
such as if someone were to use it they generate
比如如果有人要使用它们生成的
a large amount of spam
大量的垃圾邮件
so when you use these capabilities of a large
所以当你运用这些能力的时候
language model
语言模型
please
请
use it only in a responsible way and in a way that
只以一种负责任的方式使用它，以一种
helps people
帮助人们
in this video we'll go through
在这个视频中，我们会讲到
an example of how you can use a language model to
一个如何使用语言模型的示例
generate a personalized
生成个性化的
email based on some information
电子邮件基于一些信息
the email is kind of
这封邮件有点
self proclaimed to be from an AI bot
自称来自一个人工智能机器人
which as you mentioned is very important
正如你所提到的，哪一点非常重要
we're also going to use
我们还会用到
another one of the models input parameters
另一个模型输入参数
called temperature
称为温度
and this kind of allows you to
这让你可以
vary the kind of degree of
变化的种类程度
exploration and variety
探索和变化
in the kind of models responses
在模型反应中
so let's get into it
让我们开始吧
so before we get started we're going to
在我们开始之前，我们要
kind of do the usual setup
就像通常的设置一样
so set up
那就开始吧
the Openai Python package
Openai Python包
and then also define our help of function
然后定义函数的帮助
get completion
得到完成
and now we're going to write a custom
现在我们要写一个自定义
email response to a
电邮回复
customer review
客户审查
and so given a customer review and the sentiment
考虑到顾客的评价和情绪
we're going to generate a custom response
我们将生成一个自定义响应
now we're going to use the language model to
现在我们要用语言模型来
generate a custom email to a customer
生成给客户的自定义电子邮件
based on a customer review and the sentiment
根据顾客的评论和意见
of the review
评论的内容
so we've already extracted the sentiment
所以我们已经提取了情绪
using the kind of
使用一种
prompts that we saw in the inferring video
我们在推理视频中看到的提示
and then this is the customer view for a blender
这是搅拌机的客户视图
and now we're going to customize the
现在我们要定制
reply based on the sentiment
根据情绪回复
and so here the instruction is
这是指令
you are a customer service
你是一名客服
AI assistant your task is to send an
人工智能助手你的任务是发送一个
email reply to a valued customer
回复重要客户的电子邮件
given the customer email delimited by 3 baptics
给定由3个字母分隔的客户电子邮件
generate are applied to thank the
生成是应用于感谢的
customer for their review
供客户审阅
if the sentiment is positive or neutral
如果情绪是积极的或中性的
thank them for their review
感谢他们的评论
if the sentiment is negative
如果情绪是负面的
apologize and suggest that they can reach out to
道歉，并建议他们可以联系
customer service
客户服务
make sure to use specific details from the review
确保使用审查中的具体细节
write in a concise and professional tone
用简洁和专业的语气写作
and sign the email as AI customer agent
并以AI客户代理的身份签署邮件
and when you're using
当你使用的时候
a language model to
一个语言模型
generate text that you're going to show to a user
生成要显示给用户的文本
it's very important
这很重要
to have this kind of transparency
to have this kind of transparency
and let the user know that the text they're seeing was
让用户知道他们看到的文本是
generated by AI
人工智能生成
and then we'll just input the customer review
然后我们将输入客户评论
and the review sentiment
以及评论情绪
and also note that this pop isn't necessarily important
还要注意，这个流行并不一定很重要
because
因为
we could actually use this prompt to also extract
实际上，我们也可以使用这个提示符提取
the review sentiment and then in a follow up step
审查情绪，然后在一个跟进步骤
write the email
写邮件
but just for the sake of the example
只是为了举个例子
well
好吧
we've already extracted the sentiment from the review
我们已经从评论中提取了情感
and so here we have a response to the customer
这是我们对顾客的回应
it addresses details that
它处理的细节
the customer mentioned in their review
客户在评论中提到的
and as we instructed
按照我们的指示
suggest that they reach out to customer service
建议他们联系客服
because this is just an AI customer service agent
因为这只是一个人工智能客服代理
next we're going to use
接下来我们要用
a parameter of the language model called temperature
语言模型的一个参数叫做温度
that will allow us to
这样我们就可以
change the kind of variety of the models responses
改变模型响应的种类
so you can kind of think of temperature as
所以你可以把温度想象成
the degree
的程度
of expiration or kind of randomness of the model
或者模型的随机性
and so for this particular phrase my favorite food is
所以对于这个短语，我最喜欢的食物是
the kind of most
那种最
likely next word that the model predicts is pizza
该模型预测的下一个单词很可能是披萨
and the kind of next to most likely it
最可能的一种
suggests are sushi and tacos
建议是寿司和玉米饼
and so at a temperature of 0
在温度为0的情况下
the model will always choose the most likely next word
模型总是会选择最有可能的下一个单词
which in this case is pizza
在这种情况下是披萨吗
and at a higher temperature
在更高的温度下
it will also choose one of the less likely words
它还会选择一个不太可能出现的单词
it might even choose tacos
它甚至可能选择玉米饼
which only kind of has a 5 percent chance
哪种只有5%的概率
of being chosen
被选中
and you can imagine that kind of
你可以想象一下
as the model continues
随着模型的继续
this final response so my favorite food is pizza
最后的回答是我最喜欢的食物是披萨
and it kind of continues to generate more words
它还在继续产生更多的词汇
this response will kind of diverge from
这个反应会偏离
the first response which is my favorite food is tacos
第一个反应是我最喜欢的食物是墨西哥卷饼
and so as the kind of model continues
随着这种模式的延续
these two responses will become more and more different
这两种反应会变得越来越不同
in general when building applications where you want a
通常，在构建应用程序时，您需要
predictable
可预测的
response I would recommend using temperature 0
我建议使用温度0
throughout all of these videos we've
在所有这些视频中
been using temperature 0
一直使用温度0
and I think that
我认为
if you're trying to build a system that is
如果你想建立一个系统
reliable and predictable you should go with this
可靠，可预测你应该用这个
if you're trying to
如果你想
use the model
使用模型
in a more creative way where you might want
用一种你想用的更有创意的方式
a kind of wider variety of different outputs
一种更广泛的不同的输出
you might want to use a higher temperature
你可能需要用更高的温度
so now let's take this same prompt that we just used
现在我们用刚才的提示符
and let's try generating an email
让我们试着生成一封电子邮件
but let's use a higher temperature
但是我们用更高的温度
so in our get completion function
在getcompletion函数中
that we've been using throughout the videos
我们在视频中一直在用
we have kind of specified a model
我们已经指定了一个模型
and then also a temperature
然后是温度
but we've kind of set them to default
不过我们把它们设为默认
so now let's try varying the temperature
现在我们试着改变温度
so we use the prompt and then
所以我们使用提示符，然后
let's try temperature 0.7
我们试试温度0.7
and so with temperature 0
温度为0时也是如此
every time you execute the same prompt
每次执行相同的提示符
you should expect
你应该预料到
the same completion
同样的完成
whereas with temperature 0.7
而当温度为0.7时
you'll get a different output every time
每次都会得到不同的输出
so here we have
这里我们有
our email and as you can see it's different to
我们的电子邮件，你可以看到它是不同的
the email that we kind of received previously
我们之前收到的邮件
and let's just execute it again
我们再执行一次
to show that we'll get a different email again
为了表明我们会再次收到不同的邮件
and here we have another different email
这里我们有另一封不同的邮件
so I recommend that you kind of play
所以我建议你们玩一玩
around with temperature yourself
周围有温度
maybe you could pause the video now and try this
也许你现在可以暂停视频，试试这个
prompt with a variety of different temperatures
提示用各种不同的温度
just to see how the outputs vary
看看输出是如何变化的
so to summarise
总结一下
at higher temperatures the outputs from the model
在较高的温度下，模型的输出
are kind of more random
是比较随机的吗
you can
你可以
almost think of it as that at higher temperatures
几乎可以把它想象成在更高的温度下
the assistant
助理
is more distractable but
是不是更容易分心
maybe more creative
也许更有创意
in the next video we're going to talk more about
在下一集视频中，我们将更多地讨论
the chat completions endpoint format
聊天完成端点格式
and how you can create a custom chat bot
以及如何创建自定义聊天机器人
using this format
使用以下格式